<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technologies on Mach Five Marketing</title><link>https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/</link><description>Recent content in Technologies on Mach Five Marketing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mach Five Magnet - Conversational Lead Capture Flow Builder</title><link>https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/mach-five-magnet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/mach-five-magnet/</guid><description>Mach Five Magnet Turn conversations into conversions. Build engaging lead capture flows with our visual editor. No coding required. play_circle Try Interactive Demo mail Contact Sales Static Forms Leave Money on the Table Traditional lead forms kill conversions. Long, intimidating fields overwhelm visitors. Conversational flows guide users naturally, increasing engagement and capture rates by engaging prospects one question at a time. 68% Average Form Abandonment Rate 5.8% Conversational Flow Average 3x Higher Engagement Rate Build Conversations, Not Forms Create engaging conversational experiences with our visual flow builder.</description></item><item><title>Mach Five Portal</title><link>https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/mach-five-portal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.machfivemarketing.com/technology/mach-five-portal/</guid><description>Powered by Mach Five Tech Mach Five Portal Real-time notifications that work everywhere. Stream, sync, and engage your users with intelligent event delivery built for modern applications. open_in_new Visit SSE Website description Read the Docs campaign Product Announcement Built for Real-Time Everything you need to deliver intelligent, context-aware notifications that users actually want to receive. stream Real-Time Pipeline WebSocket-based streaming delivers events instantly to connected clients. Offline devices automatically sync when they reconnect.</description></item></channel></rss>